

# Işil Vardarlı JR. Backend Developer

isil.vardarli@ogr.iuc.edu.tr

isil.vardarli@ogr.iuc.edu.tr

isil.vardarli@ogr.iuc.edu.tr

isil.vardarli@ogr.iuc.edu.tr

**5**070878422

♥ Küçükçekmece İstanbul

**#** 04/05/2000

**@** Single

■ R2

Female

in www.linkedin.com/in/isilVdrl

https://github.com/isilvdrl

## **Profile**

I was born in Istanbul. I am studying Computer Sciences at Istanbul University-Cerrahpasa. I am at 4th grade right now. I am developing backend applications and api's for apps since 2 years . I worked at several school projects and companies. I am familiar with backend programming languages. I love and never stop learning.

### **Professional Experience**

06/2022 - 08/2022 Istanbul, Turkey

Jr. Backend Developer, ITU Poilabs

Developing in-company products with using .net , Node is and Html&Css , testing the software which we

produce. Creating Api's for the frontend applications

01/2021 - 09/2021 Istanbul, Turkey

Istanbul, Turkey

IUC Cyber Security Club Board of Directors, Istanbul University-Cerrahpasa

03/2020 - 08/2020 IUC Computer Club Game Development Team Board of Directors, Istanbul University-Cerrahpasa

Developing games with a squad of students. We developed 2 games together. Besides I developed 3 games on

my own while I was in this squad

#### **Skills**

Node JS **Backend Development**  Net MVC

**Backend Development** 

Html & CSS Frontend Development **JavaScript** 

**Bootstrap** 

Frontend Development

Mongo DB **Database** OOP C++ & C#

SQL

#### **Education**

09/2019 - 06/2023 Istanbul, Turkey

Computer Engineering, Istanbul University-Cerrahpasa

3.45 Current GPA

#### **Certificates**

- Cisco Networking Academy Introduction to Cybersecurity course Certificate of Completion
- Cisco Networking Academy Mobility Fundamentals course Certificate of Completion
- HCSA Intelligent Collaboration

# Languages

• English

• Turkish

#### **Projects**

# **Flying Bird**

Competitive border lining game. Try to have more points without touching the borders or falling down

# **Employee Management System**

A project which you can use to manage your employees anywhere . You can add , delete or change them via this application . This project is developed using Node.js

# **Shopping List Planner**

A project where you can store the data of your shopping lists. You can have several lists at any time and use the objects however you want. User can change between the lists and delete or add them anytime

A complicated virus game which continues on given conditions. A selected player will be infected at the beggining and this situation will effect the other players as the game goes on .

#### **Student System**

A school based project . Teachers can see and change the properties of students . The project is developed using .net C#